http://www.nwpca.com/privacy.aspx

National Wooden Pallet and Container Association
Print Page | Contact Us | Sign In | Join NWPCA
Toggle navigationMENUDirectory Search - Pallet RecyclersSearch - Buy/Sell PalletsSearch - Equipment/SuppliersSearch - PDS Licensed UserEvents Webinar SeriesAnnual Leadership Conference AboutHotel & TravelFall Plant Tours AboutPallet Design System About PDSTrainingFastenerSyncUSDA BioPreferred®PDS Reference DocumentsLicensingLocate a Licensed PDS UserRequest Free TrialContact SupportAdvocacy Issue BriefsCovid-19PalletPACThe Advocate (NWPCA Member Login)Congressional Plant Tour GuideWood Facts & FiguresOur Industry Industry & Marketing ResourcesISPM 15 & Trade Overview & TradeISPM 15 Export RequirementsLocate Heat Treatment ProviderSafety Resources Outdoor Pallet Storage - Fire Code OverviewCompliance Manual - EnglishCompliance Manual - EspanolOSHA - Worker SafetyForklift SafetyPackaging StandardsNature's PackagingPalletCentral®
Read Current & Past IssuesAdvertiseSubscribeNewsFoundation About the Pallet FoundationOur People FoundersDonorsTrusteesOur ProjectsWays to Donate Online ContributionDonate to AuctionMembership JoinRenew BenefitsManage Your ProfileAbout Our Work, About NWPCAOur Story - Pallets Move the WorldCommittees & OutreachLeadership & Staff
Privacy Policy
Legal and PRivacy
General and COVID-19 Related InformationInformation and answers to questions about COVID-19 published herin are provided by the National Wooden Pallet and Container Association (“NWPCA”) for voluntary, informational use in the rapidly evolving novel coronavirus crisis. This information does not constitute medical or legal advice, and is not a statement of the standard of care. The information is not comprehensive or continually updated. This information is not intended to substitute for the independent professional judgment of health care providers, or legal or tax advisors.
When reviewing government guidance and policy to develop company policy, companies should evaluate their specific situation based on their own facts.
The appearance of external hyperlinks does not constitute endorsement by NWPCA of the linked websites, or the information, products or services contained therein. NWPCA does not exercise any editorial control over the information you may find at these locations nor does NWPCA make any representation of their accuracy or completeness.
Please contact those websites with any questions.
NWPCA provides this information on an “as is” basis, and makes no warranty, express or implied, regarding the information, including but not limited to its completeness or accuracy. NWPCA specifically disclaims any warranties of merchantability or fitness for a particular use or purpose. NWPCA assumes no responsibility for any injury or damage to persons or property arising out of or related to any use of this information or for any errors or omissions. Use of the information is subject to the complete NWPCA website Terms of Use.
Privacy Policy and Use of Cookies
At PalletCentral.com we are committed to protecting your privacy. We do not rent or resell your personal information to third parties for marketing purposes. The information we collect is used to provide information and services to our members and those
interested in the wood packaging industry who request such information. This statement of privacy explains data collection and use in those situations. Please read this complete privacy statement.
PalletCentral.com is not responsible for the content or privacy practices of non-PalletCentral.com websites to which this Site or any other PalletCentral.com website may link. Also, PalletCentral.com is not responsible for the privacy practices of its
Members or users of its Members websites. You should review any additional privacy policy and terms of use agreements of the entity from whose website you clicked-through before using the site.
Please note that the practices of PalletCentral.com, its affiliates, and agents ("NWPCA"), with respect to data collected and used by NWPCA in connection with this website and all other NWPCA affiliated websites, and its affiliates with links to this
policy (collectively, the "Site") and NWPCA services available or enabled via the Site ("Services"), are governed by this online privacy policy ("Privacy Policy") as amended from time to time, and not the privacy policy in effect at the time the data
was collected. Please regularly review our Privacy Policy.
If you have objections to the Privacy Policy, you should immediately discontinue use of the Site and the Services enabled by the Site and follow the procedure described in the section entitled "Updating your personal information and privacy preferences."
This Privacy Policy does not govern privacy practices associated with offline activities, websites other than the Site, or any products or services not available or enabled via the Site. Notwithstanding the foregoing, to the extent that any terms
of the Privacy Policy conflict with the terms of an existing written (including electronic) agreement between you and the website from which this Policy is linked, this Policy shall take precedence as it relates to the practices of NWPCA.
U.S.-EU Safe Harbor Framework and the U.S.-Swiss Safe Harbor Framework
PalletCentral.com complies with the U.S.-EU Safe Harbor Framework and the U.S.-Swiss Safe Harbor Framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information from European Union member
countries and Switzerland. PalletCentral.com has certified that it adheres to the Safe Harbor Privacy Principles of notice, choice, onward transfer, security, data integrity, access, and enforcement. To learn more about the Safe Harbor program, please
visit http://www.export.gov/safeharbor/
PalletCentral.com has further committed to refer unresolved privacy complaints under the US-EU [and EU-Swiss] Safe Harbor Principles to an independent dispute resolution mechanism, the BBB EU SAFE HARBOR, operated by the Council of Better Business Bureaus.
If you do not receive timely acknowledgment of your complaint, or if your complaint is not satisfactorily addressed by PalletCentral.com, please visit the BBB EU SAFE HARBOR web site at www.bbb.org/us/safe-harbor-complaints for more information and
to file a complaint.
If you have any questions regarding this policy, please contact:
National Wooden Pallet & Container Association (NWPCA) 1421 Prince Street, Suite 340 Alexandria, VA 22314 USA
If you do not receive acknowledgment of your compliant or your complaint is not satisfactorily addressed by PalletCentral.com, you should then contact:
Council of Better Business Bureaus, Inc. 4200 Wilson Boulevard, Suite 800 Arlington, VA 22203 Web: bbb.org Email: eusafeharbor@council.bbb.org
Entities Collecting Personal Information
Personal information on this site is collected on behalf of the entity from whose web page you clicked-through and who is responsible for this site content and data. Please contact the organization responsible regarding collection questions and data privacy.
The site contains links to other sites at which personal information is collected. In such instances, unless expressly provided otherwise, the collection and use of your personal information will be governed by the privacy policy applicable to that site.
That privacy policy should identify the entity that is collecting your personal information.
Updating Your Personal Information and Privacy Preferences
You have the right to access and correct your personal information and privacy preferences at any time. With respect to Profile Information, this may be accomplished by linking to your account at "Edit My Profile", where you can view and make changes
to your personal information. You may also access and correct your personal information and privacy preferences (such as whether you wish to receive various communications) by writing the entity at their specified address within their contact information
page on the site from which you have clicked.
Personal information submitted through this Site or in connection with the Site that is not Profile Information or is not accessible online. To access and/or correct such information and privacy preferences (such as whether you wish to receive promotional
communications), you may write the entity of contact them via their online contact form. In your correspondence, please detail the location on this Site or otherwise where you provided your personal information. You may expect a response within 30
days. For information submitted in connection with Products and Services, you may also follow instructions included or referenced within such Product and Service to access or correct the information.
Collection of Personal Information
As a visitor to this site, you can engage in many activities without providing any personal information. In connection with other activities, such as utilizing online or hosted Services, the Site may ask you to provide certain information about yourself
by filling out and submitting a form. It is optional for you to engage in these activities. If you elect to engage in these activities, however, the Site may ask that you provide personal information, such as your first and last name, mailing address
(including postal code), country of residence, e-mail address, employer, title, telephone and facsimile numbers, and other personal information. When participating in electronic commerce via the Site, you may be asked to provide a credit card number.
Depending upon the activity, some of the information that is asked of you may be mandatory and some may be voluntary. If you do not provide the mandatory data with respect to a particular activity, you will not be able to engage in that activity.
Similarly, if you wish to delete your information (pursuant to the mechanism set forth in "Updating your personal information and privacy preferences") that is mandatory, you will no longer be able to engage in a particular activity.
When you use the site and the Services, the site may also collect certain information about your computer to facilitate and evaluate your use of the site and Services. For example, the site may log environmental variables, such as browser type, operating
system, CPU speed, referring or exit webpages, and the Internet Protocol (IP) address of your computer. The Site also uses such information to measure traffic patterns on the Site and usage of the NWPCA Services. NWPCA does not match such information
with any other information held by NWPCA unless we have your consent.
By using this site, you agree and acknowledge that personal information collected through the Site or in connection with the services provided may be transferred across national boundaries and stored and processed in any of the countries around the world
in which NWPCA maintains offices, currently only in the United States. You also acknowledge that in certain countries or with respect to certain activities, the collection, transfer, storage, and processing of your information may be undertaken by
trusted third parties. Such third parties are bound by contract with NWPCA not to use your personal information for their own purposes or provide it to any third parties.
How Your Personal Information is Used
NWPCA collects your information in order to record, support and facilitate your participation on the site from which this policy is linked. If you subscribe to or register on the site, for example, the information is used provide access to the website
and other benefits that may be made available to registered users. Your personal information is also used to track your website preferences and keep you informed within the community unless you have opted not to receive such communications or such
communications are prohibited by law.
NWPCA may collect information about the use of the Services and the site, such as the number of downloads, types of Services used, how many users we receive daily, and the IP/Internet address of your computer. This information is collected in aggregate
form, without identifying any user individually.
NWPCA may use this aggregate, non-identifying statistical data for improving the Site and Services, providing more relevant experiences to our clients and for statistical analysis.
Email communications
We do try to keep unrequested emails to members to a minimum. You will see at the bottom of every email, you have options to “opt-in” or “opt-out” of various bulletins. To do so, click “manage preferences” option on the email, and check/uncheck the various
email categories.
Use of Cookies
When someone visits this site, standard internet log information and details of visitor behavior patterns are collected. This is done to find out things such as the number of visitors to the various parts of the site. This information is collected in
a manner in which it does not identify anyone. No attempts are made to find out the identities of those visiting this site. No data gathered from this site is associated to/with any personally identifying information from any source. Cookies are small
text files that are placed on your computer by websites that you visit. They are widely used in order to make websites work, or work more efficiently, as well as to provide information to the owners of the site. Most web browsers allow some control of
most cookies through the browser settings.
Google Analytics cookies may be used on this site. These cookies are used to collect information about how visitors use this site. The cookies collect information in an anonymous form, including the number of visitors to the site, where visitors come
to the site from, browsing patterns on this site, and the pages they visited.
Please note that NWPCA is not responsible for the content or privacy practices of non-NWPCA websites to which this site or any other NWPCA website may link. Also, NWPCA is not responsible for the privacy practices of its Members or users of our Members
websites. You should review the additional privacy policy of the Member’s site in advance, and contact the organization should you have questions regarding their policies.
Sign In
Remember Me
Forgot your password?Haven't registered yet?
Latest News
more
10/6/2020PECO Pallet Announces Definitive Agreement to be Acquired by Alinda Capital Partners and USS
9/16/2020Bettaway Beverage Distributors Named as Carrier of the Year by C.H. Robinson
Calendar
more
10/13/2020Online Training: PDS Basics - Block Pallets10/15/2020Webinar: Softwood Lumber Trends
Featured Members
Windsor Pallet LimitedCelebrating 25+ Years Membership
Connections
P. MorrisJ. VeillonD. StikeleatherJ. ZhouB. TarnefJ. SullivanA. StanisciaCaledon Fire & Emergency ServicersD. PelayoD. WalkerT. LimJ. LimK. Chuy HueyL. Cheng WeiBay Cities ContainerB. SterkelB. Van BenschotenPalletPrenuerAmerican Timber & Steel Corp.T. ButterfieldB. StoutS. Dantzler YoungAGPA. TallaABC EngineeringU. GA Wright WoodworkingA. WrightJ. MerrifieldDar Al-handasah
Online Surveys
Member Educational Priorities and NeedsPDS Training Feedback Survey
National Wooden Pallet & Container Association / 1421 Prince Street, Suite 340 / Alexandria, VA 22314-2805
Tel. 703 519 6104 / Fax. 703 519 4720
Legal & Privacy Policy
Membership Software Powered by YourMembership  ::  Legal
